{
    "id": "6ab8c35985c846628ac262a96f50140f",
    "title": "Phrasal Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Are you speaking ……………………… me or against me?",
            "description": "To speak for is to speak on somebody's behalf.",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "for",
                "down"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2c340fb21eb74dc09be48055c21d2877"
        },
        {
            "question": "It is a crowded place in the evening. Don’t forget to speak ................................... a table.",
            "description": "To speak for a table is to reserve it.",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "for",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2b03a145458b4fb781250e003eafbbe3"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is a brilliant actor. His movies speak ……………………………. themselves.",
            "description": "When a story speaks for itself, it represents a certain quality.",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "for",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c896f0dd317142658271a79cdf980a82"
        },
        {
            "question": "You only have to speak ……………………………… yourself.",
            "description": "To speak for yourself is to speak on your behalf.",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "for",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f9ed40d9677b412894101b7d59e6ad7b"
        },
        {
            "question": "It was a kind gesture that spoke ……………………………. his generosity.",
            "description": "Speak of can mean indicate or suggest.",
            "answers": [
                "about",
                "of",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "40a6370141b140e091dea2f362626c2b"
        },
        {
            "question": "Be brave and speak ………………………...",
            "description": "To speak out your opinion is to assert it.",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "in",
                "up"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "579cc10e94ae4e38aac084c1d55af560"
        },
        {
            "question": "Every time I hear that song, my eyes become misty. Those lyrics really speak ................................. me.",
            "description": "If something speaks to you, it resonates with you.",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "to",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b1bc0241aa314235a9a8ed3921f35c67"
        },
        {
            "question": "I can’t hear you. Can you speak ……………………………?",
            "description": "To speak up is to talk more loudly.",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "in",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0ff2939eea7749ce9d87ee4fc766d49d"
        },
        {
            "question": "He was one of the few leaders who always spoke …………………………. for the poor and the oppressed.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "over",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "cf8c256b721c4a86b6ddc7b6656fbf9a"
        },
        {
            "question": "His conduct was despicable but I didn’t dare to speak ……………………….. about it.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "over",
                "up"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "5f463e82ed764135a888ec7360611134"
        },
        {
            "question": "You should speak …………………………. him if you don’t want this to happen again.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "to",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ef3cbceb894440b6bbab3ef0b0c52591"
        },
        {
            "question": "It was one of the driest years on record – no rain to speak …………………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "of",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4883ec2c6f1f45daa4728b6b5e61bf7c"
        }
    ]
}